Today, I've got an exciting news to share with you.
Streamlet is hosting the Lom hackathon that is happening from
September 5 to September 19. Now, before we dive
into the details of the hackathon, let's talk a little bit about Streamlet.
Streamlet is a low code web framework that allows you to create
data apps in Python using a simple API.
It's no secret that Streamlet has become the go to platform for building
LLM based apps. In fact, they already have over 12,000
apps accounting in their community, and developers
are unlocking new possibilities using large language models.
Streamlet has partnered with some of the leaders in LLM based technology,
including Lancing, Llamaindex,
AssemblyAI, Weviate, and Clarify. These partnerships
means you'll have access to top notch tools and expertise
while participating in the hackathon.
So what's this hackathon all about? It's your chance
to build a groundbreaking LOM based streamlet
app that incorporates at least one of the following LOM technologies
from these partners, including Lancing,
AssemblyAI, Wev, eight, Llamaindex, or clarify.
There will be five price categories, one for each
partner listed above, and in each category there will be two lucky app
winners. You can participate solo, or you could
also partner up in a team of two, and winners will
be announced by October 5. So if you're wondering how
your app creation will be judged, these are the criterias.
So they're looking for inventive and error free apps,
and that the app should be public on GitHub and also
hosted on the community cloud. The app should also use one
of the five partner technologies mentioned here, and bonus
points if it is addressing common LLM pain
points like transparency, trust, accuracy,
privacy, cost reduction or ethics. And here's the exciting
part. There are five most innovative used prize categories,
each category corresponding to one of the partner technologies.
And in each of the categories, as already mentioned, there will
be two lucky app winners. Aside from the special swag
from the two winning apps in each of the category,
the first 250 apps submitted will receive a pair of streamlit socks.
Yes, you heard that right, streamlet socks. Now, before you
get started, there are plenty of resources to help you on your
LLM hackathon journey. Firstly, you could join the LLM
hackathon channel on the Streamlit discord, and there are tutorial
blogs in starting with these technologies. If you
need some inspiration, you can check out the example LLM apps like
building a chatbot, building a web eight magic the gathering
chat building a chat research using LangChain using custom
data sources using Lambda index? Or how
about analyzing video channels automatically using AssemblyAI?
Or interact with models via chatbots using clarify.
When you're done with your app creation, don't forget to submit it and be a
part of this incredible LM hackathon journey. So mark your calendars.
You have from September 5 until the 19th to take
part in the Streamlit L and M hackathon. It's your chance to shine,
collaborate, and make a real impact using ln technology. I'll also be
one of the judge and I can't wait to see what you create. Until next
time, happy hackathoning.